[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 18 + 3 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "48",
      "options": [
        "48",
        "50",
        "46",
        "53"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 11 + 4 \u00d7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "27",
      "options": [
        "29",
        "25",
        "27",
        "32"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 20 + 7 \u00d7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "41",
      "options": [
        "46",
        "43",
        "39",
        "41"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 9 + 5 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "59",
      "options": [
        "61",
        "64",
        "57",
        "59"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 15 + 4 \u00d7 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "51",
      "options": [
        "53",
        "56",
        "49",
        "51"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 11 + 6 \u00d7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "35",
      "options": [
        "33",
        "40",
        "35",
        "37"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 7 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "74",
      "options": [
        "72",
        "76",
        "79",
        "74"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 2 \u00d7 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "16",
      "options": [
        "21",
        "14",
        "16",
        "18"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 9 + 7 \u00d7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "37",
      "options": [
        "39",
        "35",
        "42",
        "37"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 9 + 3 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "39",
      "options": [
        "39",
        "37",
        "44",
        "41"
      ]
    }
]